all right this is the V stance
deadlift um if you haven't seen my video
on the V stance squat please watch it
I'm posting it right before this video
but in a similar vein the B St squat I
think transfers best to The Squat and I
think the Beast Dan deadlift would be
the best single leg exercise to transfer
to the actual deadlift because when you
do it on one leg for example single leg
Romanian deadlist most most people are
limited by how much weight they can use
by how much they can balance balance
becomes an issue you don't quite feel
like you get your all out of it but when
you use the B
stance this is my normal deadlift stance
I'm just going to kind of turn this foot
out like that I might bring this foot in
just slightly and then from here I'm
trying to keep most of my weight on this
leg and just use this leg for stability
so it just goes like this
so
again keep most of your weight on this
leg this leg is just there for stability
switch
sides
and uh I think you'll find that you can
handle heavier loads with this variation
than you can the other single like de
variations thanks for watching